

**#SPECIAL** 

**RESUME** 

SKYKIM1016@GMAIL.COM (+82) 010 5843 8814



# **Sky Hanel Kim**

ICT SPECIAL FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Https://Sky-profile.herokuapp.com/

#### MY BACKGROUND

Hello! I am a professional special full stack developer who has various skills and experience to development the Back-end server API and the Front-end UI,UX for making international business webs and smartphone applications by NodeJS and React and ReactNative

#### **LET'S WORK TOGETHER!**

Email: Skykim1016@Gmail.com

SKYPE: SKYKIM881016

GitHub: Github.com/skykim1016 Mobile: +82 10 5843 8814

ADRESS: 128-1 Bokjeong-ro, Seongnam-si, Republic of Korea

Canada visa: Working Holiday Visa (For 1 year that after entered in Canada)

#### MY PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- NodeJS, Express , MongoDB
- React, Redux, Angular
- React Native APP (IOS / Android)
- Android Studio , Xcode
- NPM, Yarn, Webpack, Babel, Brew ,Git, Heroku
- PHP, WordPress, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JQuery, ES6
- Java Spring ,Eclipse, Oracle10g , Weblogic 10
- JSON, RESTFUL, JWT
- Socket I.O Chat Messenger ETC.
- Google API, AWS Server
- Slack , Notion , Zeplin
- Photoshop, Primer Pro

#### **CERTIFICATES**

- CISSP / ISC2
- SECURITY+ / CompTIA
- SCJP / Oracle
- CCNA / CISCO

#### **EDUCATION**

M.A LAW Degree , Graduated in 2018 KOREA NATIONAL OPEN UNIVERSITY GRADUATE SCHOOL

Http://www.knou.ac.kr/engknou2/

BACHELOR DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, GRADUATED IN 2011 DONG SEOUL UNIVERSITY

http://www.du.ac.kr/EN/index.do

#### **CAREER HISTORY**

#### S/W Fullstack Developer, Dec 2018 - Oct 2019

MINT INTERNATIONAL COLLEGE PTY LTD [ Melbourne , Australia ] Http://Mint-company.herokuapp.com/

- The company is servicing education and training in Melbourne of Australia
   Main task works was managing old website which is built by PHP Wordpress and development to new website
   by React , NodeJS, MongoDB and make to smartphone app by React Native
- Development environments were NodeJS / Express / MongoDB / React / Hooks / Mobx / Redux / ReactoTron
- Typescript / ES6 / NPM / Webpack / PHP WordPress / MySQL / JQuery / Babel / Amazon EC2
- Google apps ( Hangout / DOCS ) / Slack / Notion / Zeplin

#### S/W Engineer , May 2017 - DEC 2017

HYUNDAI CAT6K CO. LTD [ Monterrey , Mexico ] Http://Hyundai.com

- Dispatched for system management to vehicle factory of Hyundai in Mexico where are to Monterrey and Tijuana
- Had developed administrator business programs which were for smart factory management
- Managed DB SQL which were Oracle PL-SQL and Procedure by the Toad
- Development environments were Java Spring, / Oracle10g / React / Redux / NodeJS / NPM / BREW / WebPack / Babel / Angular / Unix shell scripting / Slack / Notion

#### Freelancer of Software Projects, 2011 - 2017

- Dispatched to lot of development projects of big companies in Korea
- Developed business solution websites and Android, IOS Apps as lot of contract project
- Java Spring / Hibernate / Eclipse / Ant / Hudson / Jboss / Jenkins / Weblogic / Oracle
- NPM / Angular / React / PhoneGap / Cordova / Ionic / Ajax JSON / JQuery / Linux shell scripting

#### S/W Web App Developer , 2013 - 2015

Korea Financial Management Centre CO.LTD Http://koreafinancenter.com/

- Had developed to financial management system by web business solution and
- IOS / Android app by IONIC
- PHP Wordpress / Angular / Node|S / Express / MongoDB / Mongoose / NPM
- JQuery / AJAX JSON / Linux / NginX / Apache Tomact

#### S/W Engineer , 2010 - 2011

FutureWiz CO.LTD Http://Futurewiz.co.kr

- The FutureWiz company is being military exception industry service for stock trading, E-learning and E-Book and online video streaming
- Had worked as system software programmer instead of military duty service in Korea for developing online softwares in company
- JAVA (SPRING) / Eclipse / Mybatis / ASP.NET / PHP / JQuery / Android / IOS / Oracle / MS-SQL







< TRAVELED COUNTRIES >









# **SKY HANEL KIM**

### DETAIL INFORMATION

#### **OVER SEA CAREERS EXPERIENCE**













#### Australia | MINT Training Pty Ltd | 2019 **ICT Programmer**

Http://Mint-company.herokuapp.com/

The company is servicing for education and training in Melbourne of Australia,

And my main task working was management old website which is built by PHP Wordpress and development to new website by React, NodeJS, MongoDB and make to smartphone app by React Native

And my sub task working was IT part management which is PC, Network, Server, Software of company

Development environments were NodeJs / Express / MongoDB / React / Redux / ES6 / WebPack / Babel

PHP / Wordpress / JQuery / Bootstrap / React / Visual studio code / NPM / YARN / BREW / Express / MacOS / Slack / Notion

#### Mexico | HYUNDAI CAT6 Pty Ltd | 2017

**Factory Computer System Management** 

Http://www.jobkorea.co.kr/Recruit/Co\_Read/C/chanryang

Dispatched as ERP system manager position to vehicle factory of Hyundai in Mexico

Development environments were Java (Spring) / REST-JSON / React / Redux / NodeJS / Express /

Oracle11 / PostgresSQL / MongoDB / Unix / Eclipse / Visual Studio / NPM / YARN

#### KOR PROGRAMMAR FREELANCE

#### **GLOBAL SHOPPING MALL HYBRID WEB APP PROJECT** KOR | THE HYUNDAI HOME SHOPPING | Feb 2016 - June 2016

Http://HyundaiHMall.com

Android Market / IOS AppStore : 현대Hamll

Had developed as project with team members to development for business websites and and the IOS, Android which are for online global shopping mall of the Hyundai company of the Korea

Development environments were Java (Spring) / Eclipse / GlassFish / WebLogic / Jenkins / Hudson / Angular / NPM / JQuery Oracle 10g / Toad / Cordova (IOS, Android) / Android Studio / X-code

#### MULTI INTERNATIONAL LOCALE LANGUAGE PROJECT

KOR | THE KT SAT | Oct 2015 - Dec 2015

Http://www.KTSAT.net

Had developed application program which is can automatically changing locale language to multi international language system in application system program

Development environments were Java (Spring) / Eclipse / Ant (Java BuildUp) / JBoss / Hudson / Jenkins / Unix shell scripting Oracle10g / Toad / PostgresSQL / PL-SQL / Procedures

#### HEALTH CARE SMART TV SYSTEM ON ANDROID / IOS / WEB

KOR | THE ITI TECHNOLOGY | May 2015 - Sep 2015

Http://ITITech.co.kr

Had serviced for health care IOT system programs which is smart TV on android OS and web business application for patient, nurse, doctor in hospitals (Health Level7, EMR, OCS, PACSS)

Development environments were Android(NFC Tag, Tv Media) / JAVA(Spring) / Angular / NPM / Linux shell scripting Android Studio / Eclipse / Nginx / L2 Switch ACL / Firewall / Network sockect IO

#### **OPEN INNOVATION WEB SYSTEM PROJECT**

KOR | THE KEPCO | Nov 2011 - May 2012

Https://tech-transfer.kepco.co.kr/main/mainPage.do

System Infrastructure Outsourcing in KEPCO (Korea Electric Power Corporation),

Had system programming for Open Innovation System Project

Development environments were Java (Spring) / Eclipse / Mybatis / JQuery / Weblogic / UnixServer

Oracle / Mybatis / PL-SQL / Procedures





#### **SKILLS**

[ WEB ] NodeJS | Express | React | Redux | AngularJS | ES6 | Webpack | Babel | NPM | YARN | Ajax JSON | BootStrap | JQuery JAVA (SPRING) | ASP.NET (MVC) | C# | PHP |

[ SERVER ] NodeJS | NginX | IIS | Tomcat | Weblogic 10 | GlassFish

[ SmartPhone ] React-Native | IONIC | Android | XML-RPC Data Driven | WebServer TCP/ UDP Socket | GPS | SQL-Lite | DDMS | LogCat | NFC | PushService | Beacon | BlueTooth

**[ Tools ]** Eclipse | Visual Studio Code | Atom | SVN | GIT | PostMan Android Studio | X-Code | Jekins | Hudson | Ant | Slack | Notion | Zeplin

[ DataBase ] MongoDB | MS-SQL | MY-SQL | Oracle Toad | Post gressSQL / PL-SQL / Procedures / RDBMS Quries / NoSQL

[ OS ] | MacOS | Linux (CentOS) | UNIX (HP , AIX) Server Config Management | FireWall | Access Control IP Table | Shell Programming | VI | SSO | SSL | SSH | NFS | DNS

## **EXPERTISE**

[ NETWORK ] OSI 7 Layer | TCP/IP | LAN | UTP | WLAN | HDLC | PPP Unicast, Multicast , Broadcast | SubnetMask | Herb | Switch | Bridge | Router | VLAN Configuration | Trunking-VTP | Telnet Command | Ping Trace | Protocol | RIP | IGRP | OSPF | ISDN

[SECURITY] Digital Security Laws

Copyright | Privacy | Hacking DDOS | Sniffing | Spoofing | ARP-DNS Session Hijacking | ICMP Redirect | Cross Site Script(XSS) | Proxy Buffer Overflow | SSO | SSL | GPKI | Cryptography (AES, SEED, RSA)

## LANGUAGES

English: Intermediate Spanish: Elementary Korean: Native

# **CERTIFICATES**

CISSP / ISC2
SECURITY+ / CompTIA
CCNA / CISCO
SCJP / ORACLE
DRIVER LICENSE OF AUSTRALIA

# **Technical Skills**

JAVA	• • • • •
REACT	• • • • •
ANGULAR	• • • • •
NODE.JS	• • • • •
HYBRID APP	• • • • •
DB-SQL	



Http://skylab-c8959.firebaseapp.com



Http://memo.vlpt.us



Http://github.com/skykim1016



# **Cover Letter**

# To whom it may concern

Thank you kindly, for taking the time to read through my resume and cover letter.

I am a professional special full stack developer who has various skills and experienced to development for the Back-end server API and the Front-end UI,UX for making international business webs and smartphone applications by NodeJS and React and ReactNative

My advantages are very wide ICT skills and experties which are Front-end, Server Side, Back-end Data Base, Network, Security via globally worked experience on over 5 years where in Korea, Mexico, Australia. and my additional advantage is proven professional international ICT certificates

Maybe you would be not need to hire many ICT guys who are the back-end developers, the front-end developers, the publisher, the IOS developers and the Android developers, because I am a special full-stack developer who can make business program web and smartphone app on NodeJS and React and ReactNative by my alone, and also I have been experience while 5 years to 10 years about developing ICT programs, and in the future, I would like to development AR, VR, MR or artificial intelligence(A.I) programs by new technologies

For working in international company, I have experienced to visited ICT companies of the USA which are Google, Facebook, Apple, Adobe, where in San Francisco, and I had traveled to lot of Europe countries where to England, Netherlands, Belgium, Luxembourg, Germany, Italy, Swiss, Monaco, France, Mexico, USA, Canada and I lived in Australia while almost 2 years

My hobbies and interests are willing to learn new technologies, I am interested regard to the artificial intelligence(A.I) and AR, VR, MR apps. I beliving that would be blue ocean markets in our future, and it would be changes our life cultures such as like Youtube and Uber, AirBnB

If you give me opportunity to fabulous work in bright future with your company then I would like to work by diligent and faithful on willing mind for your company and I would be very grateful to your company

Thank you for your time

Sincerely

Developer. Sky Hanel Kim



# REFRENCE SITES



@ S K Y K I M 8 8



PORT FOLIO SITE

HTTP://SKYPLATFORM.ONLINE



[ GITHUB ] MY SOURCE REPOSITORY

HTTP://GITHUB.COM/SKYKIM1016



[ ANGULAR + FIREBASE ] A.I CHATTING

HTTPS://SKYLAB-C8959.FIREBASEAPP.COM



I REACT + NODE.JS + EXPRESS + MONGODB 1 MEMO APP

HTTPS://MEMO.VLPT.US

# HTTP://MINT-COMPANY.HEROKUAPP.COM

[REACT + EXPRESS + NODEJS + MONGODB + ES6 + WEBPACK + BOOTSTRAP + HEROKU ]

# HTTPS://WWW.HYUNDAIHMALL.COM/

[JAVA + SPRING + ORACLE + WEBLOGIC + JQUERY +GIT ]

# MINTTRAINING.EDU.AU

[PHP + WORDPRESS + BOOTSTRAP + JQUERY + ES6